is it possible to make1 $200,000 a year
working only 10 hours a week for most
people it is not possible in fact they
have a structure of earning money which
is trading dollars for hours and even in
most business models you're not going to
be able to make that much working that
little what I want to show you here in
this video is how I have been able to
not just make 1002 200,000 even $500,000
but have a s figure business working 10
to 15 hours a week and I'm actually
strategizing right now currently I'm
going to share some of the stuff that
I'm going to be doing so that I only
have to work 5 to 10 hours a week over
the next 6 months I have my second child
on the way my uh my my wife is pregnant
and we're excited the baby comes in the
fall and so I have actually decided that
before the baby comes I will only be
working 5 to 10 hours a week during that
time period now we have a great support
system around us but I know that it's
POS possible why do I know that's
possible because I have actually helped
build multiple businesses and coach and
Mentor people to do this here's the
interesting part I love working I
actually do I really love what I get to
do for business I love creating content
like this it's incredible it's fun it's
amazing it's one of my favorite things
in the world to do
however there are limited time and
resources in the day and I don't want to
miss my children growing up and I also
want to be available to support my wife
during this time period when she gives
birth as well well as raising we already
have a 1 and a half-year-old throughout
all this process so all that to say
that's my life probably doesn't matter
to you but how do you if you go from
where you are today work only 10 to 15
hours a week to be able to make six or
even multiple six and maybe even
eventually seven figures I'll tell you
this you can do it from the beginning
and this is where a lot of people get it
wrong and they're like well that's great
you're making seven figures of course
you got the money to hire staff you got
all the resources available to you and
all the knowledge and experience to be
able to do this but what about little
old me what about normal people who
don't have all of these resources and
you don't have the mentors you don't
have all of that well here's what I'm
going to provide you here today is a
blueprint and a model that I believe
works for anybody where you only need to
work 10 to 15 hours a week in your
business now if you want to work more
than that that's great and here's the
cool part about this is that working
more than 10 to 15 hours a week produces
great returns if you got 40 60 80 hours
a week to work like if you're if you're
single if you don't have any kids I mean
my goodness knock yourself out but
here's the thing most people feel like
they have to work that much and burn
themselves out to be worthy of the
amount of money that they want to make
because that's what Corporate America
has train people is that you should only
make this much based on the effort that
you put in it's a lie it's a scam and
quite frankly I'm going to come right
out and say it it is directly connected
to the same mindset that influences a
lot of the economic models that are
opposite of capitalism let's put it that
way communism socialism and right now
today we have a mass Global
indoctrination that is getting people to
accept the fact that making wealth is
evil and that making money enough to
live off of or an abundance of money
more than you need to live off of right
I'm going to tell you this straight up I
don't need to make a million dollar or
$10 million a year nobody does to live
off of you can have an extremely
comfortable life with as many options as
you want making around 300 to $500,000 a
year in this economy with inflation and
live anywhere that you want to Beyond
about a half a million dollars CU in
with inflation those numbers are doubled
used to be about a quarter million now
it's about a half a million today the
differences in quality of life are not
that that major you just get to do
things faster as far as that goes and
the reason why you would make more than
a half a million dollars a year is not
for yourself but to leverage it into
being able to create assets and have
impact as well as vision and quite
frankly power in the world today finance
and wealth is power and it gives you
options and power so that you don't have
to be controlled
by a boss a CEO or another company okay
there are companies today that are
publicly traded that are only worth
about $25 to100 million I have friends
that run businesses that are at that
level that when you play at that game
it's a different world that you operate
in and most people especially probably
most of the people who are watching this
video you're not operating in that world
that's the world that I have operated in
and worked in um when was when did my
mom first make uh eight figures I think
it was like 2009 okay so that was 15
years ago that my family my mother some
of you all might not know who she is her
name is Sandy Kowski and she built a
business she's been she's been a
multimillionaire made no less than a
million dollars a year for every year
for the last 31 years now why am I
sharing my mom's story compared to this
well I was there along the way with her
helping her with the marketing the
strategy and all of that every step of
the way during that time period since
about 2011 okay and so it's when my mom
hit this level of making $20 million a
year in business everything changed the
the lifestyle the choices how she looked
at the world and it and it influenced
our family myself my brothers everyone
around us I'm going to be the first to
admit I live in a world that is
different than most of the people that I
coach a mentor and I have for about 15
years both mentally as well as
financially but I also have made a
commitment to this that I don't want to
live off of quote unquote mommy's money
now I have a ton of advantages and I
don't I don't negate any of that being
related to my mother and the lessons
that she's taught me but here's what I
want to do is I want to pass those on to
you how many people do you know who are
the children of multi- multimillionaire
successful business owners that have
learned the
lessons and then want to pass those on
to you and they've even been able to
apply them themselves what I want to
pass on to you is how you can make a
multi6 figure income working only 10 to
15 hours a week and this is the lesson
that I I quite frankly I learned it from
my mother and I learned it as well from
some of my best clients that I worked
with another client that I worked with
his name was Rick Pino I helped him
build his business to over $10 million a
year and I did not see that man work
more than 5 to 10 hours a week and every
single week spent most of his time with
his kids I respected it so much and I
was like okay if he could do it my mom
can do it I know anybody who wants to
build a business in this space can do it
as well and it really all just boils
down to choices and I think that's the
part that I think that we got to like
get clear in our mind is that the amount
of hours that you work is actually a
choice it's not a necessity okay there
are times where you may need to grind it
out where you may need to take a week or
two and you work full-time but you do
that so then you can pull back to work
less and we can learn to automate things
and realize that working more does not
actually produce more
finances okay you got to have that
belief for this to
work I did not have this belief five
years ago five years ago my wife and I I
was no longer working with my mom this
was in two uh 20 19 right before Co hit
and I had my own business and I was
working about 120 hours a week just to
make about a quar million dollars a year
because I thought that that's what I
needed to do to be worthy of that that's
what my belief system was attached to
and since then for the last 5 years it's
taken me five
years going through therapy working with
spiritual mentors getting quite coaching
calls with my mom where I call her I'm
like okay Mom struggling with this need
help with
this
learning what it actually takes to be
able to do the things that I've helped
other people do I've seen them do it but
I wasn't experiencing it in my own life
and now today I can I can boldly tell
you I live a life where I only work 10
to 15 hours a week and I and I make an
incredible seven figure income in our
business doing so and so here's just
just sure that validates all that for
you the possibility maybe you're
thinking that's not possible possible
for you okay I want to prove that to you
that it
is there are things right now that you
know that you could do that would make
you more
money but you're not
doing because you would lose
friends you would lose family members
your reputation would
change how people view you would change
your life would
change but you know that it would
produce more financial results for
you and you're not doing them because
you want to avoid all of those other
side effects from
happening I'll tell you this you don't
need to blow up your life for this to
happen I used to think you
did you don't need to lose everything
for this to happen I used to think you
did what it takes is you raising
yourself up to a new level of
being let me explain what this
means when
I come here to make content for you I
cannot operate in the same Consciousness
that I did 5 years
ago why because that would attract the
type of people that I was attracting
five years ago I me showing up as the
version of myself that was
making A4 million dollars working 120
hours a week
we that's a person that I don't want to
be ever
again and I had to make a decision that
who I was in that moment in
time that Jeremiah's gone and he's never
showing up
again and so I want to ask you this
question there's a version of you in the
future that I believe if you're watching
this right now and you're still
listening to me it's 10 minutes in this
video statistically about 80% of
everybody who started this video didn't
even get to this 10-minute point of the
video because probably they were either
annoyed didn't believe it's possible
pissed off or they just got
distracted okay the fact that you're
listening to me right now shows and
validates that you have an inkling of a
belief that this is possible for you to
be able to make
10,000 20,000 $30,000 a month
working just 10 to 15 hours a week but
can I tell you
this what you've been doing up to this
moment in time right now isn't going to
get you there or you would have been
there
already and I used to hear people to say
that all the time to me and it would
piss me off it would make me upset i' be
like but I know that I know that I know
how to get there and I was
like but yeah but the evidence in my
life shows that I don't actually know
how to sustain it and be consistent with
it
and so one of the first things that you
have to be when it comes to creating
this in your life is you have to
be
consistent a person of your word
somebody who does what they say they're
going to do somebody who is willing to
show up even when you maybe don't feel
like it you figure out how to get
yourself to that place that's going to
help you show up for me personally I've
had a rough the last 3 days it's been
tough okay okay didn't make content for
the last two days and I knew that I had
to make this video so what did I do I
have a routine that I go through it's
about an hour long and it gets me into
the right State of Mind to be able to
create
content and so I had to be consistent to
to to figure out how to move the puzzle
pieces in my life to allow
me to do that for consistency I haven't
worked for like two days at all I don't
need to explain why to you but there's
good reasons okay
and so me actually showing up to record
this video is a level of
consistency I did
over a thousand videos for three years
one 10minute video a day for three years
I did a podcast every single week for
four
years
consistency I've shown up every single
week for my coaching group consistency
I've consistently marketed my business
and ran Facebook ads to get more people
on my email list consistency here's the
problem most people only show up and do
one thing one time and because it didn't
work out how they wanted to they don't
like it so what ends up happening is
there's a snowball effect that happens
and the snowball starts to get bigger
and bigger and bigger as it rolls down
the hill it starts to get larger and
larger and larger and when this snowball
gets larger the amount of hours that you
need to put in for the output is much
lower because it's leveraged so you're
creating leverage in your life and in
your business through the actions of
consistency most people give up get
distracted come up with good reasons why
they can't do the things that actually
work and then when they start doing a
little bit of the stuff that works they
start to get a little bit of motivation
and then a block comes in a roadblock
and they literally repeat the same
patterns over and over and over again
and what ends up happening is that their
life is a series of false starts a
little bit of
motivation and then something happens
demotivated little bit of motivation
demotivated and they end up literally
less and less and less and less because
they find that they just want to stay in
this safe comfort zone where they're not
disappointed and we're afraid of getting
disappointed by going Beyond this level
right here this becomes our limiter okay
so we all have what's called an upper
limit to where we can go with our
actions and there's a great book called
the big leap by gay Hendrick I'm a big
fan of this book I've read it over 20
times and it helped me for the first
time in when I was selling courses have
my first $20,000 month in my own
business after leaving my mom's business
was after reading this book right here
so I'm going to pull it up for you the
big leap conquer your hidden fear take
your life to the next level the idea is
and I love the picture is getting out of
your smaller
Fishbowl and into the
larger Fishbowl whoops let me pull this
over here right there okay and so the
the analogy of like the larger smaller
Fishbowl all of that the reason for this
is because
that's exactly what the experience is if
you're watching this on video you can
see it the cover of the book is a is a
fish leaving a small Fishbowl and going
into a larger Fishbowl by jumping from
one Fishbowl to another and so the
concept that I'm going to I'm going to
be sharing with you right now is is is
it's borrowed from that book a little
bit but I'm I'm going to condense it
down and kind of teach it in my own way
so we all have this sort of upper limit
that ends up blocking us every time we
want to go to a new level in our our
life and we have to actually make a leap
to go up to the next level and at that
level at each level there's always going
to be an upper limit is what it is
okay there's always an upper limit
problem I've never met anybody who
doesn't have repeated upper limit
problems the book talks about this as
well is that even billionaires have an
upper limit problem of what it takes to
go from 1 billion to 10 billion to
50 billion in their companies 100
billion 300 billion there's an upper
limit problem when it comes to their
thinking their mindset and then their
doing and their action taking as far as
that goes and so you got to really
identify what that is and usually it's
related to some kind of a fear worry
something that we want to avoid
happening something that we have been
trained mentored in it's been ingrained
into our thought process that we can't
do because it's an immovable belief
system okay and so I'm going to I'm
going to use some chat GPT here to just
kind of save us some time by the way
this is this is one way that I love
using chat GPT I'm just going to show
this to you right
here what are the four limiting beliefs
from gay
hendris the big leap it's going to give
us a list so the four limiting beliefs
are this feeling fundamentally
flawed the belief Bel of disloyalty and
abandonment the belief in the virtue of
suffering and the crime of outshining
and for me personally I suffered from
the crime of shining and disloyalty and
abandonment
fear so basically our upper limit
problem manifest in one of these four
ways for most people
okay number one fear of being
fundamentally flawed this means that
deep down you think that there is
something fundamentally wrong with you
that makes it to where other people can
succeed and you
can't and that you don't deserve it and
it leads to self-sabotage because you
think that just people like you that
have gone through your experiences just
don't succeed and I meet a lot of people
where this is their thinking okay I'm
here to tell you this today that there
are people that had it harder than you
that struggle with you that had less
skill set that are succeeding way
greater and they made a choice to not
let this belief system control their
life and to actually real Iz that
they're not fundamentally flawed that
they're actually a beautiful wonderful
creation that can do incredible things
greater and Beyond what they ever
imagined by adopting what is called a
growth
mindset a growth mindset is
this there's a difference between what's
called a fixed mindset and a growth
mindset okay you might be watching this
right now and you may have what you
think is a fixed mindset or you think is
a growth mindset but you're being
limited by fixed mindset Bel beliefs
okay I know a lot of people with the
growth mindset I was one of them who had
certain immovable beliefs that were
fixed so what it was was my overall
mindset was a growth mindset but there
were certain areas that were fixed for
me and often times one of the words that
I see a lot of people use with a fixed
mindset is two of the words
wisdom and
Excellence they believe that they can't
do certain things in their business
because it's wisdom not to do them and
that it's a spirit of Excellence to do
things a certain way and yet often times
those very beliefs are what actually
prevent them from going to the next
level we make things way too black and
white we limit ourselves based on the
should dos in
life one of the biggest things we have
to do is we have to get rid of often
times in our thinking I should be doing
this
and just eliminate that and just say you
know what I didn't do it I want to do it
let's figure out how to make it happen
and what's stopping me because what
happens is when we say I should be doing
something we end up going
into um
self-criticism as well as even sometimes
self-punishment and and what that
actually does is IT wires the brain to
create a stronger fixed mindset so you
really want to like let go of all of the
limitations that we end up putting on
our ourselves should dos is a big
limitation um sometimes our convictions
and standards are certain
limitations sometimes our fear or our
own Pride can be a
limitation what we believe is wisdom can
be a limitation managing our reputation
can be a
limitation Spirit of Excellence can be a
limitation now hear me
out before you shut me out here I think
all those things are great I think
Integrity having character operating in
wisdom having a spirit of Excellence is
great
okay I think you should take pride in
your work I think a little bit of fear
can be healthy keeps you alive okay so
like hear me out that these aren't bad
things that I'm talking about here but
what ends up happening is is they become
much greater than our own ability to
take action and they get wired into our
neurotransmitters to where we know what
we need to do but we have a series of
beliefs that become like these these uh
locked doors in our
lives and so we live can't break past to
the next level because every time we run
into a a hard stop of things we we like
immovable I just can't do that people
like me don't do that things and so one
of them is just if you believe that
you're completely flawed that's one of
them the other one is disloyalty and
abandonment and this one is rooted in
the fact that we don't want to betray or
abandon the people our family and our
peers by becoming too successful
people who got us to where we are
today and I dealt with this one for a
long time and I had to realize and every
every business owner has to realize this
that for you to go to the next level
there will be people that will be left
behind and that's not a bad thing and
you're not betraying people by doing
that and often times especially if
you've been betrayed before this one's
going to be a big one this one was one
of the biggest ones for me I had a major
abandonment wound inside of me growing
up uh my mom was in and out of different
uh Medical Treatments and I as a as a
young child one two three years old was
left with my grandparents and I felt
abandoned throughout that time period
that wires the brain of a of a of a
person very uniquely if you study brain
science and and I didn't have a father
um so raised by single mom pretty much
raised by grandparents aunts and uncles
till I was about 4 years old that wired
me to a I'm afraid of being abandoned
and I don't ever want anybody else to
feel that way and I don't ever want to
be disloyal to all these people around
me and then what ended up happening was
realizing that I'm surrounded by a bunch
of people that don't actually have my
best interest in
mind they're not helping me and they're
actually hindering me and stopping me
from growing and I'm staying silent and
not saying things and not doing the
things that I need to do
simply because I'm
afraid of how people will perceive me
and how they might treat me and how they
might see that I'm treating them now of
course it's great to care about people
and to be kind and
compassionate but you might need to
leave your buddies from high school
behind you might need to leave your
girlfriends that you meet with every
single week behind to go to the next
level can I tell you
that I had to I had friends I was
drinking with all the time partying with
smoking weed with doing all all manners
of stuff I'm not proud of and that was
my lifestyle when I was DJing and
partying and I had to leave that behind
to go to the next level in my
life I had to leave stuff behind when we
had a we had a child born I had to tell
clients Hey listen I'm no longer working
40 hours a week my availability is now
10 to 15 hours a
week and people weren't happy and they
were pissed and they let me know how
pissed they were that I was no longer
committed and and and even being accused
of being unkind and uncaring about
people and caring more about my wife
than people that I made commitments to
quote unquote now first off this was
manipulation that people were throwing
at me I very clearly expressed all of
this to people I told them this upfront
they were using my desire to help people
and my I I was dealing with people
pleasing to manipulate me to not spend
time with my wife and kids and to give
my time to them because they could
benefit from it and there are people in
your life that will do that they will
try to convince you that it's wrong to
go after your dreams they will try to
convince you that it's wrong to work
Less
hours to prioritize your
self-care why because they benefit from
you not doing that
and you might have to have tough
conversations even with the people in
your own
home for this to happen but it's worth
it now another one is this is the belief
in the virtue of suffering is that
suffering is virtuous and if we start to
succeed that subconsciously
unconsciously we're going to create more
problems that are going to actually
cause more suffering for us and that if
we that if we start having too much
success that we end up going back into
the familiar State of Mind of what feels
right and where suffering is can I tell
you this suffering has a
benefit to to to motivate you to go to
the next level but it's not
necessarily the main goal to sit in I
used to think this I grew up in a church
that taught us this belief system called
called worm theology this idea that that
we're like lower than dirt and that we
should dislike
ourselves doesn't even match scripture
or or what Jesus taught and yet this is
what they taught me growing up as like a
four-year-old in church so I had this
belief system that I couldn't like
myself that I couldn't have pleasuring
pleasurable experiences that I couldn't
enjoy things like certain foods movies
music video games and how many of you
have actually
believed that it's better to suffer to
reach your goals and to not do anything
that's enjoyable but to stay disciplined
on your goals can I tell you
this stop making rules over yourself
like this let go of all the stuff that
everybody around us tells us that we
need to and must and should
do in order to be
happy and realize
that what all we're looking for is
happiness and just do more of what you
want to do when's the last time that
you've answered this question for
yourself what do I really want to
do what do I want to do if I want to
play a video game for an hour two hours
by the way that's what my shirt is it's
from this video game series the Zelda
series if I want to watch
sports great there are mentors out there
that will teach you that it's wrong to
engage in entertainment
I don't believe that I actually believe
that having enjoyable time playing with
my son hanging out with with my wife and
by the way my wife and I enjoy watching
sports together my son enjoys watching
them with us my wife and I enjoy
watching movies TV shows playing video
games reading
books and what I found is
that discipline is important discipline
is freedom self-discipline is massively
important you need to discipline
yourself to do the stuff but you also
need to loosen up a little bit let go
let loose have fun and play a little bit
more and you will
see your your brain will literally wire
itself to be more effective in your
working time if you do
this so a little bit of a deeper
conversation for another time I'll
probably do a whole video on this Con
concept because it it might take me like
an hour to unpack why that works but it
does it really does and just learning to
have more fun and more happiness and
more enjoyment and even if you can't pay
your bills and you're losing your house
and you're you're struggling in your
marriage did you know that you can still
stay happy and that's not a bad thing it
doesn't mean that you're crazy it's
actually a good thing we have been
taught trained and wired
by quite frankly people that want to
capitalize on our sadness marketers that
want want to capitalize on our sadness
and some of
them are inside of our communities that
we're a part of because they want us to
feel more sad so they can sell us more
products see what I'm saying the happier
you are the more powerful you are and
the more effective you are with the time
that you
have and then the last upper limit uh
the the last one in the big leap is the
crime of out shining I dealt with this
one a lot
so believe that revolves around the fear
of if we shine too brightly it'll make
others feel inferior jealous resentful
and'll lead to rejection isolation I
didn't want to be abandoned I didn't
want to be isolated and I don't want
anybody to feel like I was showboating
or better than them or smarter than them
or trying to prove that and I always
would lower myself down to the level
that I would be accepted by
everybody I'm not a
politician I know how to make crazy
amounts of money in business and it
comes from being willing to just shine
as brightly as
possible and when you do that when you
are as happy as possible when you shine
as brightly as possible when you really
do what you're called to do and you're
in your zone of Genius as it as he calls
it in the big leap you're going to
irritate some people you're going to bug
some people you're going to have some
people that are just they can't stand
you because you're just too
much be too much for some people you're
not too much for yourself and you're not
too much for the things that you're
called to
do I hope this encourages some of y'all
to just go out there and be a
lot and then every time that you hit a
limit where you're like oh I got to
shrink back become aware of it one of
the ways that I do this when I feel like
I'm shrinking back is I will actually
open chat GPT up I worked with a
therapist for 5 years but I will open
chat GPT up and I will start dialoguing
with the AI and I'll say hey I was in
this situation I was feeling really
confident then this happened and I'm got
knocked down to another level of how I'm
feeling and I feel like there's an
underlying limiting belief here can you
help me identify it that one prompt in
chat GPT and then answering back and
forth with it can literally help you
unlock certain beliefs that will help
you in your life okay so all of this to
say is that when you can learn to set up
your boundaries to be willing to say no
to all the people and stuff that are
trying to pull you and obligate you to
do things trying to get you to spend
your time and your money with them and
you and you learn to identify what are
the upper limit beliefs that are
preventing me from actually doing the
things that I need to do in my business
it shrinks the amount of time that you
need to get stuff done very quickly and
then the second part is this identifying
which actions in your business produce
the greatest results okay
so this is the Practical strategy side
of things I spent the last 30 minutes
explaining the mindset spend probably
the next 10 explaining the strategy side
of it okay cuz that's exactly what this
is is you got to get to the mindset
where you can actually do these things
but oftentimes it takes a little while
to get there so you got to look at in
your business what are the things that
are going to produce the greatest
results for you number
one grow your email list
and this could be email as well as text
message
Community okay this could also even be a
school
Community uh school is a platform that
Alex Heros and Sam ens have this could
be a Facebook
group you're growing your audience
you're building your community this
could be a Facebook page this could be
an Instagram following and quite L you
want to grow all of those at once a lot
of people are like well which one should
I do first you do all of them at once
because if you're doing it right they
all kind of grow together and they're
different places where you're now
showing up in a way that is
Omni present okay so omnipresence is
what you want we used to call this
multi-channel marketing where you're
showing up in all channels in front of
people not just one at any moment in
time so what you do is you might bring
people in through one channel social
media Facebook group Facebook ad email
list joint venture podcast ebook audio
book any of these things but then you're
bringing them into a deeper level of
your community which might be a school
Community or Facebook group and then
you're directing them to sign up to your
email list this allows you to then build
an audience inside of the social media
algorithms that you can then train to
show promotions to a very targeted group
of people that are just like those that
are in your community okay so what are
you actually showing these people to
build this well you need to have an
offer you need to have some kind of an
offer that people want you cannot grow
any Community any business or make six
figures working 10 to 15 hours a week
without having an offer off that can pay
you that and it doesn't have to be a
high ticket offer it doesn't have to be
$10,000 so for instance think about this
okay if you
get sales sorry my throat was getting a
little drive if you get 10 sales at
$10,000 a year that's $100,000 a
year and if you only have to work 10
hours a week to get 10 sales of $110,000
a year you made 100 Grand that's called
high ticket okay I like to do mid tier
ticket and low ticket where we might
bring people in on a $7 or a $27
offer we might even have a free offer
right here something that's free like a
download or an ebook or a course or an
event and then we upgrade people to a
$500 to A2 ,000 offer and you can make
six figures off of this right
here and then above that you might have
a 5k 10K $20,000 offer on top of that
and that becomes the Ascension model
that helps you do this okay so all of
this you got to have stuff to sell at
the right price point with an offer that
people are actually going to buy and you
might be saying well listen my people
aren't going to buy stuff at that price
point so then you got to create an offer
that they will buy at that price point
point you might need to change
Industries niches businesses you might
need to sell something differently if
you're in a service-based business
you're trading dollars for hours and so
it might be better to where you could
figure out how you could Mentor other
people in the service that you know how
to do and then you can either certify
people earn a royalty off of their
commission some way that you can
leverage your time and investment so it
doesn't come from your actions every
single day okay so with this this is
exactly what you need to do is you need
to develop some kind of an offer that
that you can sell to people that they
will pay you that level and then we
start marketing it to people to get
customers to get clients pulling in
traffic of people that actually want to
buy or register for one of these offers
and this is exactly what I Mentor people
in in my client growth accelerator
program this is exactly what I teach in
all the videos that we create whether it
be on my podcast
whether it be on this channel right
here and so again I'd love to see you
join us in my client growth accelerator
right now you can't register for it the
doors are closed to it over at my
website Jeremiah Kowski decom you can
find it right here under coaching group
coaching and you can join the waiting
list to my client growth accelerator
program where we work with you to help
you grow the amount of clients that you
have that are willing to pay you this
much money you are going to have to
elevate yourself to the level of maybe
you're saying well right now I could not
charge that much or I don't know if I
could if I know enough people to build
an audience that I could sell a $27
product to make that much money with
great you might not today but you can
get mentored on how to do that and
that's exactly what I walk people
through is I come alongside you in your
business to work with you to install
this entire system in your business to
help you craft the right offer develop
the right product put together exactly
what people are going to buy to take
what your strengths are what your best
niches what your topic is whatever you
do maybe you do Home Inspections you
could turn that into a home inspection
certification you can mentor other
people on that you might also be able to
take your skill sets and translate it
over to a different business or
different business model the one the
business model that I like the most is
online subscriptions and memberships why
is that because what you get to do is
you can have people join you once they
pay you monthly and you're delivering
consistent content and you're not having
to wonder fight ORF flight or the launch
model of am I going to make enough money
this month to be able to pay the bills
you have consistent income coming in
even in feast or famine and this allows
you to create a very sustainable
business for yourself and this is what
we've helped a lot of people do in their
businesses is be able to create
something that they can truly rely on in
all econ Economic Times economic Seasons
whether it be up up times or down times
and be able to create the kind of income
that they want to create and have the
lifestyle that they want to have here's
the problem most people don't know how
to do this they've not ever been taught
it most people charge millions of
dollars for this type of
information
literally and in my accelerator
program the cost of it last time we
opened the doors it was $197 a month for
people that that were able to join and
be a part of it and and so again doors
are not open right now but if you do
join the waiting list we can help you
put together your messaging your offer
your offer stack to help you put to to
dial in your sales to help you figure
out how to get more people in front of
you to build your community so that you
have consistency so that you have
Clarity and focus to be able to create
that financial and time Freedom that you
might be wanting listen this doesn't
work for everybody I know that it's not
for everybody but if you're watching
this video right now maybe you got to
this point in time I would love to see
you at least join our waiting list and
jump in when we do next open the doors
for my accelerator program so that we
can help you put together an offer that
you can put together that's omnipresent
to help you grow an email list so that
you can market and sell to people
whatever your product service is that
you want to create some kind of a
continuity model something where people
will pay you and they'll stay on board
monthly as far as this goes you know
pest control my wife and I we we um we
were looking at different pest control
companies you know they charge you
hundreds of dollars a month to come take
care of different pests and stuff in
your home and we were like you know
maybe we could do this ourselves as far
as this goes well guess what we found a
different membership that sells the
products that they ship you every single
month as far as this goes so there's
where there's a will there's a way to
create businesses that you can
sustainably create subscriptions and
memberships around and be able to sell
sell products or services to people okay
whether you're doing coaching whether
you're doing mentoring whe you got a
physical product that you ship out like
a box of goods or things like
that this works and this is what we help
you with to put together in your
business all right so listen I'd love to
help you with this subscribe to my
channel if this has helped you in any
way and and let me know below what are
your questions that you have about what
I just talked about today what would you
like me to break down in a future video
what would you like me to kind of break
down in another video to show you
exactly what it takes to be able to put
one of these together I want to actually
break down the individual pieces of all
of this for you here on this channel
right so that even before you join a
mentoring program or a membership or my
coaching program with me and we walk you
through all this process and we actually
work with you through building it and
putting together I want to show it to
you for free here on my YouTube channel
as well okay so leave a comment below
let me know what would you like me to
teach in a future video and listen if
this has helped you as well share it
with somebody I'll talk soon with you
see you on the next video have a good
one